Yes, so yesterday's talk was a bit too much.
Yes. Yesterday's talk was a bit too much fun.
I'd like to continue the talk again.
Yay!
Well, there's a paper with the theme picture in it.
That's right.
Well, I'll draw first.
I'll draw first.
Then!
Okay. There you go.
What do you pay attention to when you watch other idols perform?
Wow, I see.
That's exactly what I did when I saw Uka's live the other day.
I was really impressed with the formation of the young girls.
Oh, really?
Yes, yes, yes.
We have a lot of people here.
So there's a lot of movement in the formation.
That's why I pay attention to my group.
So when I look at other groups, I pay attention to that too.
You're right, there's a lot of movement in the formations.
That's right.
So many!
You know, there's a lot of distance between them.
That's a lot.
That's what I thought.
On a big stage, for example...
What's the number, say, five?
Then, when you move from one end of the stage to the other, you have to make a dash for it.
That's right.
But if you dash too fast, it won't look good.
If you go all out, people will think you're having a field day.
Just be smart about it.
Move smartly but quickly.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
I see it, I see it, I see itI see it, I see it, I see it.
But I think it's beautiful.
I tend to look at it from above.
If I have to go on a tour...
So I thought it was really beautiful.
Thank you.
When I see Tohoku-san's live performance...
There are a lot of people, right? So many people.
But the pressure of the songs and the dance performance is so overwhelming.
It's always overwhelming.
Really?
It's amazing.
And the strength of each singer's voice.
I think it's amazing.
Like, when they're singing.
Like, what kind of dance moves are they doing here?
And so on.
And if it's other idols...
I mean, other idols, they would have some kind of stirring effect, right?
Like in the song.
Like, "Here's where the excitement starts.
I might pay attention to that.
But... aren't you genuinely enjoying it?
Fun?
It's different from us.
There's a difference between doing it and watching it.
I wonder what it's like.
I wonder.
Because we're doing it.
The technical aspects...
And MCing.
I wonder what the MC is doing.
I pay so much attention.
It's hard.
Wait a minute... what was that?Wait a minute, what was that?
I don't know.
What do you pay attention to when you see other idols live?
What do I pay attention to when I see other idols live?
But really...
I mean, I could say "everything" if I wanted to.
For example, if you're watching a video or something...
The way they look at you when they look at the camera.
Like, "Oh, this is how she smiles.
"This is how he decides what to do.
I might look at it a lot.
I know, right?
I'm going to say all of this.
I'd say all of them.
I'm not sure which one in particular.
But the formations?
Dance?
Performance?
Performance, yes.
I'm sure you're right.
You want to learn.
You want to.
You want to steal.
You want to incorporate it...
You're going to perform?
You're going to?
I'm the one who's going to do it.
I think it's a performance.
Okay, let's do it.
Okay.
Pay attention to other idols when you see them perform.
I'm sorry.
A-ha-ha-ha!
I was paying attention but couldn't say it.
I couldn't say it either.
Well, we're good friends.Well, we're good friends.
Yes, we even bite together.
Okay, let's do it again.
Ready?
What I pay attention to when I see other idols perform live
is the performance
is
That's right.
Then, one more thing...
Shall we go one more?
I don't know.
Thank you.
Then, please.
Yes, sir.
Which one is it?
Ta-da!
What do you keep in mind when you're at a benefit?
I'm a ____.
Oh, my, oh, my, oh, my, oh, my.
A benefit event.
Privilege meeting.
That's what I've been doing lately.
Yeah, it's basically like a send-off.
Thank you for saying bye-bye.
And then we say bye-bye, and then we take pictures with the members.
And then there's a photo shoot with the members.
And I don't know...
There's also the soakle book.
I've done Lilybelly before.
I don't know... we did a thing where we'd press your back with a magic hand.
What's that special event?
You've released something?
with a first single
Tailwind is a song that's a tailwind
Tailwind" is a song about a tailwind.
Oh...Oh!
I mean, it's a song named after that song.
It would be nice if we could have a benefit party for that song.
I see.
Even when that happens...
That would mean that the audience would have to...
Turn your back
And say, "Go for it.
With a magic hand.
Push?
No pushing.
No pans or anything like that.
Tell him to go for it.
Oh, my God.
Like, "Hang in there.
But really, in the lyrics of the song Tailwind.
"Hang in there" appears three times in a row in the lyrics.
I want to do my best for that video.
I'd like to make a video of him saying "Hang in there, somehow, somehow, somehow...
I'd like to make a video of it.
I see.
It's been interesting lately.
What are you doing?
You were really weird before.
You know what?
I'm not making this up.
I've been working on it.
I'm not making it, I'm not making it.
or a video of me throwing water balloons at a customer.
Summer.
The benefit concert was famous for being a little different.
Recently... there was Corona.
Yes, yes, yes.
And a glue show...
And the glue show.Like a glue show.
That's the basic idea, right?
Well, it's becoming more and more so, but...
But there are times when you need to talk.
At the day-care center, too.
And when we have storytelling sessions.
One of my shortcomings is that I can't hear what you're saying even though I'm listening to you.
I'm listening to you, but I can't understand what you're saying.
I have a title.
I'm listening to you, but I'm not listening to you.
I'm listening to you and you're listening to me.
What? There are times when I have to listen again.
I'm just trying to focus on what you're saying.
The sheet.
Right.
Since I'm on the seat...
There are times when it's hard to hear, right?
Recently, it's been removed.
And the masks have eased up.
That's true.
Yeah, yeah.
Next.
I know what you mean.
But it's like, I'm talking to you and you're like...
I'm talking to you and you're like, "Uh-huh," and I'm like, "Well, that's a different response.
I think it's definitely different when you feel it.
I know.
I think you're asking me a question.
But there's so much noise around you.
I couldn't hear what you were saying.
I'm like, "I know, right?" in response to a question.
Ah! I'm listening!
There are times like that.
It happens sometimes.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.Excuse me, sir.
Listen to me carefully.
I'm concentrating... on one thing.
I may be trying to focus on one thing.
Yeah, maybe I do.
But I don't know.
I don't know.
The clients that come to see me... they're my friends.
It's like I already have a sense of them.
I remember their names.
It's like...
Like I remember their names because they're my friends.
That's how I feel.
I think it makes me happy to be remembered.
I try to call him by his name
I try to call him by his name.
Like, "Ah!" or "Say!" when he comes over.
Or if it's the first time...
What's your name?
I try to remember.
That's what I'm trying to do.
Oh, really?
I don't have a good memory.
I'm so sorry about that.
I don't have a name.
I have to remember names.
Me too.
One of our members
Akane Sora is really good at it.
I know you're good at it, and so am I.
She's really good at it.
Did you cut your hair? or "Your makeup is different today.
Or if it's a girl...
Different color contacts? Or something like that.
Seriously? That's it? Yeah.
It's amazing to hear them say that.I was amazed to hear him say that.
The ability to see is amazing.
I think it's amazing.
I've been with... members...
I'm in a group with a member.
I sometimes think she's amazing.
I know, I know.
It's depressing, isn't it?
Ha-ha-ha.
I couldn't notice.
I couldn't help but notice.
I do that sometimes.
Sometimes.
I think it's important to treat each person as an individual.
It's one on one.
During the scoring session...
That's why...
What's that?
What do you keep in mind at scoring sessions?
What sounds best?
What do I do?
I'm just trying to listen to what you have to say.
And remembering names.
I'll remember.
One by one
one by one
face to face
Is it heavy? Is it heavy?
Even with one person who may be important
It's to face each other.
Okay, let's do it here, shall we?
What I'm trying to do in the scoring session is...
I'm conscious of each and every one of you.
Face to face.
That's right
Ha-ha-ha-ha.Ha-ha-ha-ha.
It's important to face it.
That's great.
Now, all the talk we've had so far...
Come on.
I don't know.
Did you get it?
You're more serious than I thought.
Serious
Because I haven't even spoken to Rin Waka yet
We haven't even hung out yet
I think we can have a deeper conversation.
We can
Okay, then
Last question...
Okay.
Okay, here's the one I just got.
What's the last one?
Well, here it is.
Speaking of things you should take with you on an expedition...
What's that?
Oh...
Expedition.
I wonder...
Wow, that's a lot.
It's called a "staycation".
I do that.
In May... in Lilywega...
You know...
When we did it outside of Kanto...
Four nights, five days.
It was 4 nights and 5 days.
It was the biggest one for us too.
I'm a bit of a worrier.
with that.Hold that.
So, for example, your eyes... they're white.
They're not good, so you take your contacts with you, right?
You take, say, five days' worth of contacts.
But you need 7 days' worth, like a week's worth.
It's important.
You never know when they'll come off.
You might bring too much.
You might be taking too much with you.
So you have a lot of luggage.
I see.
Who has less?
Maybe Ayame?
I don't think so.
I don't know.
Seems very minimal.
That's exactly what I'm talking about.
Ruri...
Pillow to sleep on the plane.
I wonder if it's called a pillow.
Like a neck pillow.
The sky is the most...
The sky is the most.
I asked her what she had in her purse.
I asked him what he had in there.
For TikTok.
And some shoes and clothes for college.
I wondered why he was taking it with him.
I was like...
So you have a suitcase?
Or maybe it's Sware.
I see.
It's a bit of a divide, isn't it?
Who has the most suitcases?Who's up for more
Mew.
I don't know...
You know, when you go through the airport...
How many kilometers do you have to go?
Like "heavy".
I'm followed every time.
What about your carry-on?
It's really big.
And... you know, I like flashy things.
Like pink.
Yeah, it's really easy to tell.
It's like, "Hey, that's Miu Miu!
It's easy to spot.
That's true, Mew.
She's got all kinds of things.
I don't know what it is, but...
I don't know what it is, but he's got all kinds of stuff in there.
I wonder what he puts in there.
I don't like to carry too much stuff.
I like to keep it to a minimum.
But...
But when I see a member with a lot of stuff...
I feel like I forgot something.
I can see that.
Like, do I need something?
I'm not sure if that's true.
But I always bring my pajamas.
Wait, we're together.
I'm with you.
That's what I'm talking about.
You know what?
You already have them at the hotel.
But then I wouldn't be able to sleep.
I know, I know.
I'll definitely bring my pajamas.I'll definitely bring my pajamas.
I want to bring my pajamas.
That's it. That's it.
I'll definitely bring my pajamas.
I'll bring my pajamas, too.
Really...
That's why when I had a lot of luggage...
I'm always asked what I'm putting in my pajamas.
I'm told I don't need pajamas.
I can't sleep without them.
I can't sleep.
Pajamas.
Okay, here we go... pajamas.
Okay.
Speaking of things you should bring on an expedition...
Pajamas.
No, these...
What we have in common
More and more!
So we talked again
It was a lot of fun!
We talked about all kinds of things
We were able to talk about things that happen in each other's group
We could talk about each other's groups and so on.
Great, great, great!
It was great!
Tomorrow, we'll be back with more of our conversation.
Please look forward to it!
So far, I've been talking with Waka Yasumori of Ginari Tohoku
Waka Yasumori and
and Miki Murahoshi of Ukka.
See you tomorrow.